Register to The Kay Swift Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, 1911-1986; Series I; 4.6' (11 boxes)
  - Stage Works, I.A
    - [Alma mater. Invitation to bicycle ride] Invitation to ride "Bicycle built for 2.", 1 manuscript piano score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 2-3.
      2 copy, 1 photocopy (complete)
    - [Alma mater. Invitation to bicycle ride] Two on a bicycle., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 27)
      Page 2 is unidentified vocal score.
    - [Alma mater. Nightmare], 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil and black ink.
    - [Alma mater. Offbeat Waltz] Offbeat waltz / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript piano score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Unidentified sketches on p. 2 verso (dated: 9/19)
    - [Alma mater. Opening] Alma mater: Opening (football), 1 manuscript piano score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Holograph in ink.
    - [Alma mater. Salvation Army Sal], 36 p. of music; various sizes. (Box 3, Folder 31)
      8 versions (some incomplete, some sketches)
      Original and photocopy of 1 version have different annotations on 1st page.
    - [Alma mater. Salvation Army Sal (Sketches)], 16 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - [Alma mater. Selections, arr.] Janitor's polka / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript score (4 p.) + 4 manuscript parts; 36 cm., 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Holograph in pencil, annotations in ink.
      Arr. for: clarinet, piano, double bass, and percussion
      Parts are copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil and pasted in.
      With: Waltz for a dancer.
    - [Alma mater. Selections, arr.] Waltz for a dancer / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript score (11 p.) + 4 manuscript parts; 36 cm., 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Holograph in pencil, annotations in black ink.
      With: Janitor's polka.
    - [Alma mater. Villain (Sketches)], 8 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 34)
      Miscellaneous sheets.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Candles] Candles / lyric by Rumer Godden; music by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 35)
      For proposed musical based on Rumer Godden's A Candle for St. Jude (see 12/15)
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Candles] Candles., 1 manuscript condensed score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 35)
      At top: Intro.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Candles], 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 35)
      Incomplete, lacks all before last p.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Candles], 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 35)
      Vocal line with text and chord symbols.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Felix's song] Felix's verse., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 36)
      Lacks text.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Hilda's song] Hilda's song., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Lollie's song] Lollie's song., 1 manuscript vocal score (7 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 38)
      Includes percussion cues.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Madame's song] Madame's song., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Sixpence and a smile] Sixpence and a smile., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Swan ballet] Start of Swan Ballet., 1 manuscript condensed score (8 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Stage direction at top of page 1: (Leda gathering shells)
    - [Candle for St. Jude. Unidentified song], 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 42)
      First line: A little star, Her name in lights.
      At top: (pizz accomp.) Lion.
    - [Candle for St. Jude. When we dance] Love song: "When we dance.", 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - [Century 21] Century 21: Original sketches., 1 manuscript piano score (43 p.); 33 cm. (Box 3, Folder 44)
      Holograph in pencil, annotations in red and blue pencil, and red and blue ink.
      Spiral bound.
      For 2 pianos.
      Address label on cover: Kay Swift 400 East 59 Street New York 22, N.Y.
      Written to underscore Seattle World's Fair exhibit, 1962.
    - [Century 21], 1 manuscript condensed score (various pagings); 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 45)
      Copyist's manuscript (photocopy), annotations in pencil.
      Numbered pieces corresponding to bound piano score in 3/44: 1. 2. 3. 4. 6. 7.
      Pieces not in bound score: Education. Worry music. 5. Computer music. 5. Computer music (20A).
      Found in folder marked: FOR ORIGINAL MSS. R.R.B., SEE R.R.B'S DIRECTIONS ON THIS SCORE. h.g. OOPS, SORRY, ROBERT RUSSELL h. [R.R.B. is Robert Russell Bennett; h.g. is probably Hunter Galloway, Kay Swift's 3rd husband.]
    - [Century 21. Computer music] Computer music / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript score (16 p. in various pagings); 44 cm. (Box 26, Folder 712)
    - [Century 21. Computer music] Computer music., 1 manuscript piano score (7 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 46)
      Instrumental cues indicated.
    - [Century 21. Computer music] Computers., 1 manuscript piano score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 46)
      Incomplete, lacks all after p. 5.
    - [Century 21. Opening] Century '21 / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript score (14 p.); 44 cm. (Box 26, Folder 713)
      Holograph in pencil, annotations in red ink.
      Incomplete, lacks all after p. 14.
      2 copies of page 1 and 6 copies of page 2 laid in.
    - [Century 21. West wind waltz], 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 31 cm. (Box 3, Folder 47)
      Note at top of page 1: Used for Seattle Fair. [West Wind Waltz (crossed out)]
    - [Century 21. Worry music], 1 manuscript piano score (3 p.); 36 cm. (Box 3, Folder 48)
      Copyist's manuscript (photocopy), annotations in red pencil.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. (Sketches)], 13 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 49)
      Holograph in pencil and blue ink.
      Bicentennial presentation for the American Medical Association, written by Frederick Feirstein with Alfred Stern.
      1 page dated: 5/17/1974; May 22.
      1 page dated: 5/25/1974.
      1 page dated: 6/9/1974; 6/10/1974.
      1 page dated: June 12: 74.
      1 page dated: Nov. 14 just before midnight.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Busy doctor] Busy doctor., 1 manuscript score (3 p.) + 1 manuscript part; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 50)
      Part for violoncello.
      Part is copyist's manuscript in ink.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Contemporary M.D.] Contemporary M.D., 1 manuscript score (3 p.) + 3 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 51)
      For flute, clarinet, violoncello, and piano
      Parts for: flute, clarinet, and violoncello only.
      Parts are copyist's manuscript in ink.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Contemporary M.D.], 2 p. of music; various sizes. (Box 3, Folder 52)
      Holograph piano score in pencil and ink.
      2 versions, both incomplete.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Contemporary M.D.], 3 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 53)
      From 3 different incomplete scores.
      For flute, clarinet, violoncello, and piano (1 for harpsichord)
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Cue sheets], 2 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Dr. Rush theme] Dr. Rush, theme 1., 1 manuscript score (4 p.) + 1 manuscript part; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 55)
      Middle of p. 3 marked: Rush Theme, Version 2 from letter A.
      Part for clarinet only.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Dr. Rush theme] Dr. Rush-theme B., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 55)
      For flute, oboe, violoncello, and harpsichord
      Incomplete, lacks all after p. 2.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Dr. Rush theme (Sketches)], 3 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 55)
      Fughetta (Rush theme)
      1 page dated: 6-19-1974.
      1 page dated: 6-21-1974.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Rainy night on Second Avenue] Rainly night (earlier version), 1 manuscript piano score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 56)
      Dated: July 5.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Rainy night on Second Avenue (Sketches)], 4 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 57)
      Holograph piano score in pencil.
      Instrumental cues indicated on both.
      1 page dated: April 11.
    - [Dr. Rush pays a house call. Sad Yankee Doodle] Sad Yankee Doodle: Section 1., 1 manuscript score (3 p.) + 2 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 58)
      Parts for: flute, oboe, and clarinet only.
      Parts are holograph in pencil.
      Flute part includes: Dr. Benjamin Rush. Busy Doctor.
    - [Fine and dandy], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 3, Folder 59)
      Holograph in pencil (some photocopy)
      Guitar symbols in blue pencil.
      Includes ukukeke tunings.
      Order for this and all subsequent entries derived from 3 programs in the Yale collection: Schubert Theatre, Newark, week of September 8, 1930; Erlanger's Theatre, New York, week of October 6, 1930; Erlanger's Theatre, week of November 24, 1930.
      Contents: Rich or poor (photocopy). Fine anddandy [on cover: Engraver: Kindly insert refrains marked 1 + 2 as is with the music. And print Refrains marked 3 + 4 on back page.] [separate note: Parts of the 3rd and 4th choruses don't fit. Please mark in on proof Engraver]. Starting at the bottom (photocopy). Can this be love? [on cover: Engraver: Kindly leave room for 2nd verse. (Henri Klickmann 550 West 158 Street [crossed out])]. Let's go eat worms in the garden (photocopy). The jig-hop. [Not listed: Nobody breaks my heart (on cover: Text missing page 5) (possibly song listed in September 8 program entitled "I'll never break his heart")]
    - [Fine and dandy], 1 manuscript vocal score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 3, Folder 60)
      Holograph in ink (some photocopy) and copyist's manuscript (photocopy)
      Contents: Machine shop opening (photocopy). Rich or poor (photocopy). I'll hit a new high (2 copies, 1 photocopy with annotations in pencil). Let's go eat worms in the garden. Picnic song (2 copies, both photocopy with annotations in ink) [possibly song listed in programs as Act II opening]. Let's go eat worms in the garden (photocopy). Jig-hop (3 copies, 2 photocopy with annotations in pencil). [I'm afraid I'll have to fall in love (photocopy) (possibly song listed in September 8 program entitled "Time to fall in love")] Wedding bells. Wedding bells [starting p. 2A] (2 copies, both photocopy with annotations in pencil and ink). [Not listed in programs: Additional couplet for "Whoa, there" (2 copies, 1 photocopy with annotations in pencil)]
    - [Fine and dandy], 1 manuscript piano score (various pagings); various sizes. (Box 3, Folder 61)
      Copyist's manuscript (photocopy)
      Lacks lyrics.
      Contents: Machine shop opening and chant. Rich or poor. Fine and dandy. Can this be love? I [sic] hit a new high. Jig-hop. [Not listed: Etiquette]
    - [Fine and dandy (Sketches)], 4 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 62)
      1 page dated: Jan. 4, '75.
    - [Fine and dandy. Can this be love] Can this be love / lyric by Paul James; music by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 63)
      Accompaniment is different from published sheet music in 4/64.
      Paul James is the pseudonym of James P. Warburg, Kay Swift's first husband and collaborator on The Little Show, Garrick Gaieties, Nine-Fifteen Revue, and Fine and Dandy.
    - [Fine and dandy. Can this be love?] Can this be love? / lyrics by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 64)
      2 copies (1 photocopy)
    - [Fine and dandy. Can this be love (Sketches)], 5 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 65)
      At top of 1 page: fragment of "Yes, I Shall" (dated: '72) (see 10/316)
    - [Fine and dandy. Fine and dandy] F. and D., 2 manuscript vocal scores (2 p., 3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 66)
      Acc. arr. for 2 pianos.
      Both incomplete: one lacks all after p. 2, one all after p. 3.
    - [Fine and dandy. Fine and dandy] Fine and dandy / words by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 30 cm. (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - [Fine and dandy. Fine and dandy (Sketches)], 3 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 68)
      1 page dated: Friday, 11, 22, 1974.
      1 page includes "Can This Be Love?"
    - [Fine and dandy. I'm afraid I'll have to fall in love]
      See [Fine and dandy. Machine shop opening] (4/71)
    - [Fine and dandy. Jig-hop] The jig-hop / lyrics by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 69)
      Photocopy.
    - [Fine and dandy. Let's go eat worms in the garden] Let's go eat worms in the garden / lyrics by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - [Fine and dandy. Machine shop opening], 4 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 71)
      Same as Machine Shop Opening in 3/61.
    - [Fine and Dandy. Machine shop opening] Opening., 1 manuscript part (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 71)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil and ink.
      P. 2 contains "I'm Afraid I'll Have to Fall in Love."
    - [Fine and dandy. Machine shop opening], 1 vocal score (8 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 71)
      Computer generated score.
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1-2, p. 4-5, and all after p. 8.
    - [Fine and dandy. Nobody breaks my heart] Nobody breaks my heart / lyrics by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - [Fine and dandy. Rich or poor] Rich or poor / lyrics by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 30 cm. (Box 4, Folder 73)
      Annotations in pencil and ink.
    - [Fine and dandy. Say Joe] Say Joe., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 74)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink.
      Melody line in different ink.
      Annotation in script (13/26, p. 1-26) indicates this song belongs to Fine and Dandy.
    - [Fine and dandy. Sing high] Fine and dandy: Tag to Sing high / Spialeck [sic]., 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - [Fine and dandy. Sing high] Sing high / Kay Swift; Paul James., 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 75)
      Listed in program of September 30, 1930.
    - [Fine and dandy. Starting at the bottom] Starting at the bottom / words by Paul James; music by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 76)
      Copyist's manuscript (photocopy).
    - [Fine and dandy. Starting at the bottom] Starting at the bottom / [music] Swift; [lyrics] James., 8 p. of music (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 76)
      Holograph vocal score in ink.
    - [Fine and dandy. Starting at the bottom] Starting at the bottom / lyrics by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 77)
      2 copies (1 photocopy, annotations in pencil)
    - [Fine and dandy. Selections, arr.] Fine and dandy: Selection / music by Kay Swift; arranged by Hans Spialek -- New York: Harms, 1930., 1 piano score (11 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 78)
      Contents: Fine and dandy. Can this be love. The jig-hop. Starting at the bottom. Rich or poor. Let's go eat worms in the garden.
      Dated: 12-11-30.
    - [Fine and dandy. Selections, arr.] Fine and dandy / Kay Swift; arranged by Hans Spialek., 1 manuscript piano score (15 p.); 34 cm. (Box 4, Folder 78)
      Compiled from copyist's manuscript and published sheet music.
      Note on page 15: Please Mr. Drexler and gang print this page a little Broader.
    - [Fine and dandy. Selections, arr.], 2 manuscript scores (11 p., 8 p.) + 14 p. of manuscript parts; 36 cm. (Box 4, Folder 79)
      Both incomplete: Fine and Dandy lacks all after p. 11, Can This Be Love? all after p. 8.
      Arr. for: voice, piano, double bass, and percussion.
      Parts for double bass only, some inconsistent with score.
      Parts are holograph in pencil and ink, annotations in ink and pasted in.
      Note on last page of 1 part: Homer: After this chorus, the rest is a pizz. accomp. to a sung chorus, probably in E-flat. Any suggestion as to key for you being changed, or preference as to pizz. over arco will be welcomed Kay Tempo is approx. 108=[half note], but not any faster.
    - [Fine and dandy. Wedding bells] Wedding Sequence., 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - [Hello, Expo 'Sixty-Seven!] Hello, Expo 'Sixty-Seven! (Bonjour, expo 'soixante-sept!) / music and lyrics by Kay Swift + Hunter Galloway., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 33 cm. (Box 4, Folder 81)
      Copyist's manuscript (photostat)
    - [Here's the pitch. Baseball, baseball] Baseball, baseball / lyrics by RALPH FREED; music by KAY SWIFT., 1 manuscript vocal score (10 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 82)
      Written for a proposed musical television series about baseball by Kay Swift and Alfred Stern (see 13/34)
    - [Here's the pitch. Baseball, baseball], 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 83)
      Hologragh in ink, annotations in ink and pencil.
      Vocal line, with text on [p. 2] only.
    - [Here's the pitch. Baseball, baseball], 2 manuscript parts (2 p., 2 p.): 32 cm., 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - [Here's the pitch. Baseball, baseball (Sketches)], 1 leaf of music; 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - [Here's the pitch. Unidentified (Sketches)], 2 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 86)
      First line: Settin' in the dugout.
      1 page dated: Aug. 10.
      2 p. dated: Aug. 12.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music], 1 manuscript vocal score (28 p.) + 3 manuscript parts; various sizes. (Box 4, Folder 87)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil and red pencil.
      Music for play by Marc Connelly.
      Order derived from annotated script and cue sheet in 13/36.
      Parts for: vib., violoncello, and piano [note at top: (Note: This is to be played, throughout, 2 octaves higher than written. It is marked "16.")]
      Parts are copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
      Contents: Look skyward: music-box arrangement, Act One Scene I. Windborn voices [at top: Act I and Act III]. The pipes in the dew. Look skyward. Verse to "Look skyward" [top of page 1: (solo for "Cynthia," act II) II-15]. Chorus of "Look skyward," solo for Cynthia, for Act II [note at top of p.: (NOTE: This is a segue from the copy marked "Verse to Look Skyward" Upbeat and word "Look" is on copy marked VERSE to LOOK SKYWARD.)]. Look up, look out [at top: (Act II) II 24 II 34]
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music] "Hunter's moon": Incidental music for the play of that title by Marc Connelly. / Music by Kay Swift: used in London production., 1 manuscript vocal score (17 p.); 33 cm. (Box 4, Folder 88)
      Holograph (photocopy)
      2 copies, bound.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music (Sketches)], 7 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 4, Folder 89)
      Includes some unidentified sketches and "Bonus Baby."
      1 page dated: Sept. 20, '56; Sept. 21, '56.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Look skyward / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript chorus score (5 p.) + 5 manuscript parts; 32 cm., 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 90)
      At top of page 1: voice parts only.
      For Cynthia, Mezzosoprano, Alto, Baritone, and Bass.
      Parts are copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil and ink.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Look skyward., 2 manuscript vocal scores (4 p., 4 p.) + 1 manuscript part; 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 91)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil.
      Vocal duet for Cynthia and Prudence.
      Part for harpsichord (includes vocal line and text [at top of page 1: REFRAIN FOR 2 VOICES])
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Look skyward., 2 manuscript vocal scores; 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 92)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in ink.
      Parts for: harpsichord and voice.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Look skyward / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 33 cm. (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Verse to "Look skyward," and refrain. (solo and harpsichord), 1 manuscript vocal score (6 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 93)
      P. 3-6 lacks text.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Look skyward., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward], 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 93)
      At top: Added 8-bar coda, D-major chorus ("Look Skyward")-Cynthia.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Moon of green leaves / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 94)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look skyward] Look skyward / music and lyrics by Kay Swift -- London: Chappell, 1958., 1 vocal score (3 p.); 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Look up, look out], 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.) + 1 manuscript part + 5 fragments of manuscript parts; 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 96)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil and blue ink.
      Part for harpsichord.
      Fragments are parts for: Mezzosoprano I, Mezzosoprano II, Alto, Baritone, and Bass.
      Fragments are holograph in blue ink, annotations in pencil.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Piper in the dew] The piper in the dew., 1 manuscript chorus score (4 p.) + 5 manuscript parts + 1 manuscript chorus score (1 p.) + 5 fragments of manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 97)
      Note at top of page 1: (new version of accompaniment for piano-harpsichord; vocal parts same as original)
      Parts for: Soprano I, Soprano II, Mez., Tenor, and Baritone.
      Parts are copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil and blue ink.
      Chorus score (1 p.) is holograph in ink [note at top of p.: Hummed section, a cappella, "Piper In The Dew," Letter D]
      Fragments are holograph in ink, annotations in pencil.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Piper in the dew] The piper in the dew / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Piper in the dew] The piper in the dew., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 35 cm. (Box 4, Folder 97)
      Includes "Sing Joyfully Now."
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Ritual dance], 2 manuscript parts (2 p., 1 p.); 31 cm., 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 98)
      Copyist's manuscript in pencil and blue ink.
      Parts for percussion.
    - [Hunter's moon. Incidental music. Windborn voices] Windborn voices / Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript chorus score (6 p.) + 5 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 99)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
      Parts for: Soprano I, Soprano II, Alto, Tenor, and Baritone.
      Parts are holograph in ink, annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
    - [Little show. Can't we be friends?] Can't we be friends? / Kay swift; Paul James., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 100)
      Holograph in ink, annotations pasted in.
      Part for double bass.
    - [Little show. Can't we be friend?] Can't we be friends? / words by Paul James; music by Kay Swift -- New York: Harms, 1929., 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 4, Folder 101)
      2 copies
    - [Little show. Can't we be friends? (Sketches)], 1 leaf of music; 32 cm. (Box 4, Folder 102)
      Dated: Jan. 8th '75.